demacmedia.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Bounteous

## Introduction

Bounteous (“we”, “us” or “Company”) respects your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. 

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our website [www.bounteous.com](http://www.bounteous.com/) (the “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.  

This policy applies solely to information we collect: 

  * on this Website 

  * in e-mail, text, and other electronic messages between you and the Website 

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website or application operated by us or any third party, or 

  * any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible or recommended from or on the Website 

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using the Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.  

## Children Under the Age of 13 

The Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under the age of 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [bnt-privacy@bounteous.com](mailto:bnt-privacy@bounteous.com). 

## What information do we collect about you and how do we collect it? 

We collect certain types of information from and about users of our Website, including information: 

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, or telephone number (“personal information”) 

  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as your internet protocol (IP) address and geolocation information; and 

  * about your internet connection, the equipment, operating system, and browser that you use to access the Website and usage details 

We collect this information: 

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us 

  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies 

### Information You Provide to Us.

The information we collect on or through our Website may include: 

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time you submit a contact or information request form, register to attend a training session, or subscribe to our e-mail newsletters. We may also ask you for information if you report a problem with our Website 

  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us 

  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders, such as when you register to attend a training session hosted by us 

### Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including: 

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, geolocation data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website 

  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type 

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking).  

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may include personal information, or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. This information helps us to improve our Website and to deliver better and more personalized services by enabling us to: 

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns, such as how often you visit, where you go on the site and what you do 

  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests 

  * Speed up your searches 

  * Recognize you when you return to our Website 

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include Cookies and other tracking. See our [Cookie Policy](https://www.bounteous.com/legal/cookie-policy/) for details.

## Connecting To Google Applications 

Bounteous hosts several tools and calculators on [www.bounteous.com](http://www.bounteous.com/) that provide the ability for visitors to connect to certain Google products, like Google Analytics. Different Bounteous tools may ask for different permissions, so it is important to review the requested permissions before allowing access. 

### How It Works 

In order for these Bounteous applications to work properly, a user must begin the process by clicking the ‘Connect’ button. The user will be taken to a secure page on Google.com via a new window or tab, where the permissions the tool requires will be displayed. If the user consents to grant Bounteous' permission, Google will issue a token that our tools can use to access the requested information. 

For these tools and calculators, Bounteous only requests temporary access to a user’s Google application. After receiving permission, Bounteous can, within the scope of the approved access, request information about, or data from, any account the user has access to. By default, our access to a user’s information expires after one hour. 

By default, our tools are able to see the email address of the of the user's account, if the user opts to use our tools and provides authentication. We do not capture or store this information on our servers. Our tools do not ever see or store a user’s password, as that is entered on a secure window or tab on Google’s website and is not visible to us. 

As no information is stored by default, no Bounteous employee or other individual has access to user email addresses or the results of the tools, including the data received from Google, unless the user explicitly opts-in to sharing results via email or signing up for email newsletters. 

We do not request the ability to extend the lifetime of the token (termed ‘Offline Access’). We do not store or receive the token on our server anywhere; the token itself is only accessible by the user’s browser. 

To monitor which tools from Bounteous, and others, have been granted access to your information, and to see which permissions have been granted, review your connected applications here: <https://myaccount.google.com/permissions>. 

### How Do We Use The Information? 

The information that we request is used by our tools in calculations and visualizations about your selected data. Again, we do not store your information by default; however, depending on the tool, we may ask if you would like to share or email the results of your information. If offered, this step is voluntary but may allow us to receive a copy of your information so that we may provide recommendations, analysis, or follow-up support regarding your use of the tool or your individual results. If you share your results with others via email, or specifically ask for Bounteous to follow-up, we may follow up infrequently to offer support, answer questions, or offer services. 

## Customer Email Lists 

Bounteous maintains several email newsletters to help communicate information about our recent blog posts, upcoming trainings, and other general informational and marketing purposes. You can opt-out of these electronic communications at any time by following the instructions in our emails. 

When you register for blog updates, we will send you content related to your choices. At any time, you may update your subscription settings to change the frequency or types of emails, or opt-out completely of these electronic communications by following the instructions in our emails or by emailing [bnt-privacy@bounteous.com](mailto:bnt-privacy@bounteous.com). 

### How We Use Your Information 

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information: 

  * To present our Website and its contents to you 

  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us 

  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it 

  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any content, products or services we offer or provide though it 

  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website 

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information 

  * For any other purpose with your consent 

  * To subscribe you to our newsletter or email updates if you register  

  * To send you information about a training for which you have registered 

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties’ products and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please click the unsubscribe link in an e-mail (see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information). 

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display interest-based advertisements to our advertiser’s target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria. 

## Disclosure of Your Information 

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated within this policy or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. We may disclose personal information that we collect or that you provide as described in this privacy policy: 

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates 

  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business 

  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred 

  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures (see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information) 

  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it 

  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information 

  * With your consent 

We may also disclose your personal information: 

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request 

  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes 

  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction 

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information 

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:  

  * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly 

  * Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can also always opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [bnt-privacy@bounteous.com](mailto:bnt-privacy@bounteous.com). 

  * Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your contact information used by us to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [bnt-privacy@bounteous.com](mailto:bnt-privacy@bounteous.com). If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may opt out of future e-mails by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the promotional email. Please note that this opt out does not apply to information provided to us as a result of a product purchase, product service experience, or other transactions 

  * Targeted Advertising. If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any advertising e-mails you receive. For this opt-out to function, you may need to temporarily set your browser to accept browser cookies 

We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) on the NAI’s website. 

### Accessing and Correcting Your Information  

You may send us an e-mail at to [bnt-privacy@bounteous.com](mailto:bnt-privacy@bounteous.com) to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We may delete or destroy your personal information and we may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this privacy policy. Please note that we cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. 

## Data Security 

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.  

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website and the Company is not and shall not be responsible for any loss or fraud as a result of such circumvention. 

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy 

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. We will not reduce your rights under this privacy policy without your consent in accordance with applicable law. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address that you have provided to us and/or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes. We will keep prior versions of this privacy policy in an archive for your review.  

## Contact Information 

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us:  

By email:  [bnt-privacy@bounteous.com](mailto:bnt-privacy@bounteous.com). 

Or write us at:  Bounteous, Attn: Privacy, 2100 Manchester Road, Building C, Suite 1750, Wheaton, IL 60187 USA
